thenibs.org 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | TheNibs.org

  * Privacy Policy

TheNibs.org - Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

At Thenibs.org we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, when ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.

Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie which enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To send periodic emails, the email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements and .

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act).

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us:

support [at] thenibs.org

**NOTE:**  
**1.** Users posting non-English links, their account will be terminated immediately.  
**2.** Posts are screened regularly for spam content, so do not post irrelevant links.  
**3.** Also, try to post the Titles in Title case.  
**4\. You need 2 votes to get on homepage.**

An upcoming web 2.0 social bookmarking website where you can share your favorite sites. Submit, Comment and Vote. You can even share videos from popular sites like Youtube. 

* * *
